See you next time.
Give us your answer, Robin.
The Straw Hats outcry.
Listen up, all of you.
We're putting Nico Robin out of Straw Hats' reach immediately.
Come with me to the Gates of Justice.
Bring the prisoners.
But, but Chief.
No buts, just do it.
Well, there's one giant butt that's a big problem.
What the hell is that?
Oh.
Hey, Sponda.
Like you said, I'm pretty much screwed.
So I figured I might as well blow myself up, you know?
What?
That way, at least I get to take your sorry ass with me when I go.
You fool!
Wait a minute, will you?
When my butt goes off, the explosion's going to be at least a mile wide.
Not much point in running, but you might as well try.
I don't know what's going on in your pants, but please make it stop!
Three, two...
Dammit, I can't die in a time like this!
Why?
Stop it!
Time to go, Robin.
Coup de...
Boom!
Good.
The chains are broken, too.
We're falling!
You burn!
That was a close one.
Good thing that fence was there to catch us, huh?
Hey, you didn't get hurt, did you?
If I had another bottle of cola, I could get us to the other side with a coup de vent.
Hey, check it out.
Straw hat's over there.
Now's your chance.
Better give him your answer.
He tricked us!
Chief!
Frankie and Nico Robin broke the chains and went out on the balcony!
Then what are you waiting for, stupid?
Capture them already!
If you let them get away, I'll send you all to the gallows!
What?
Hey, Robin!
You're still there!
Didn't you hear me yelling?
Rufy.
Don't let them get away!
Grab them before they run!
I don't have time for you thugs right now!
Weapons left!
Ah!
Guess that means Frankie's there, too.
Oh, okay, I'll be right over!
It's a little far, but I can make it!
Now, let's go for a PhD!
And then, let's go 2004 to my perfect assassin!
How could you score anyway?
Now, let me give you a message.
Don't let them go!
And then, let me give you a message.
Come, come!
Stop it!
What?
Topic!
Huh?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'm not coming back. I'm not part of your crew anymore.
Just go away. I don't want to see your face ever again.
Don't you understand?
Why did you come to save me in the first place?
Why can't you just let me go?
You never asked for this.
You've gone too far.
For the last time.
I don't want you here.
Do you hear me?
I just want to die!
Now this is entertainment!
What a twist!
What the hell are you trying to pull?
Your friends put their lives on the line to come here!
And you...
They decided to do that on their own.
Are you kidding me? Who cares?
You're in the way.
What's wrong, Kaku?
Vincent, your anger?
Cause your devil fruit powers are so lame?
Oh, shut up already.
I like my powers just fine.
Oh, all this ruckus for one little pirate.
Yo-yo!
Alone though he may be, his perseverance is certainly admirable.
I'll be damned so he beat Bluno after all.
Ha ha ha!
What a fool!
Being a barkeep for five years probably didn't do his fighting skills any favors.
So it would appear, but it's still a surprise.
Either way, he lost.
Cha-ba-ba!
Ha ha ha ha!
I'm glad you could all make it, CP9!
And just in time, too.
It seems the Straw Hats are having a little tiff.
It's quite amusing.
Ha ha ha ha!
You really shouldn't miss it!
There's a shortcut there, Yokozuna!
Keep it up!
Get up!
Ha ha ha!
Guilty!
Yes!
It's a guilty cherry!
Step aside!
It's time for that frog to hear its verdict!
Grrrr!
Guilty!
Just what we need.
More weirdos!
Guilty!
Let's get him, Chopper!
Wait, I mean, go get him, Chopper!
What?
Me?
Alone?
I gotta admit, I never thought there'd be an actual judge on this island.
I heard that the people who get taken here are already considered guilty.
So the Marines just lead the poor saps to an empty court without even stopping.
I'm afraid you're mistaken, Pirate.
On the contrary, this courthouse carries the integrity of the greatest authority in the
world.
Even scum like you are given a trial by jury.
However!
The jury here consists entirely of former pirates who have been condemned to death row in this
very courtroom.
Therefore, their only desire is to drag others down with them.
This place really is the gate to the underworld, isn't it?
Thus, in all the trials carried out on this island...
Not once!
Has any criminal been found not guilty?
Kill me!
Ah!
Oh no!
Guilty!
Damn, they're too strong!
We can't give up now!
If we don't bring down that drawbridge, it's all over!
Remember, Straw Hat is the one who's going to rescue our bro!
If we can't help him with this, then we have no right to call ourselves the Frankie family!
Yo, Cassandra!
You took all those blows for us and never punched an inch!
All of it's you!
Ha ha ha!
Don't bother!
We've still got 6,000 marines!
Now, let's storm the courthouse and crush those pirates!
What's going on?
Why are the Giants here?
It's the Frog!
Huh?
What's the situation here?
Wait, I know you!
here wait I know you you're with the straw hats what do you do with those
giants can't believe he held off all those marines on his own yeah he's one
hell of a frog
where'd they run off to they must have gotten lost again we don't have time for
this crap oh yeah as long as I go up everything should work out fine
We'll be right back.
Don't get cocky with me, you stupid pirates.
I have the power to put you in your place and I'm not afraid to use it.
You wouldn't.
I'll wipe them out just like your hometown Ohara was wiped out 20 years ago.
The buster call is mine to command.
Stop it.
Anything but that.
On the next, One Piece, Robin's past.
The girl who was called a devil.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.